shinystat.com 2009-06-10

# ShinyStat™, privacy policy - customers and users Privacy.

The text below is not a contract, but is meant to provide important information. Shiny srl undertakes to process personal data correctly and in compliance with the law, and is committed to upholding its Privacy Policy as described below: 

\- The **VISITOR** is someone surfing the Internet via their own browser, who, of his/her own accord, visits the page of a website on which ShinyStat's HTML code is placed.  
\- The **USER** is someone that uses the ShinyStat service, either for free or upon payment, in order to monitor the visits to its site. 

Visitor Privacy

The technology developed by Shiny srl for its monitoring and analysis system allows users to record the flow of visits to their website **without using any tool that can be used to personally identify the individual**.   
The methodology used for collecting data is, in fact, only able to provide information regarding the visits and the paths taken by visitors through the website **and cannot be used to trace the identity of the VISITOR as data is collected in an aggregated way and in real time** using cookies (*) and stored on Shiny srl servers. Data collection and processing **is carried out absolutely anonymously** and is aimed at providing ShinyStat's USERS with quantitative information on visits made to their websites. (*)Cookie: original numerical code randomly assigned to the VISITOR's browser during each visit to a website. The same VISITOR, in compliance with the law, **can disable** this function, preventing the above-mentioned operation from taking place 

Customer and User Privacy

The only personal data (**) managed by Shiny srl are those collected when the USER registers with our service: we hereby specify that data defined by Law 675/96 as "sensitive" **are not requested**. Shiny srl will only process these data in order to fulfil the legal obligations deriving from this contract, to which the USER of ShinyStat, in its various versions (Free, PRO, Business and ISP), is party.   
In order to develop a closer relationship with its USERS, Shiny srl will process these data, upon explicit authorization, also for promotional operations aimed at advertising the innovations of our product range 

**Shiny srl guarantees the USER that the data collected in order to study VISITOR behaviour will be analysed in an anonymous and aggregated way**. Shiny srl is fully committed to improving the protection level of its information and telecommunications instruments in order to maximize their security.

For any further information or to cancel data supplied upon activating the service please contact: [privacy@shinystat.it](mailto:privacy@shinystat.it "send a email") . 

(**)Personal Data: Surname, first name, sex, date and place of birth, address, tax code and VAT number
